Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 4 Month(s)

Highest Degree: PG Diploma [Advanced Computing]

Notice Period: 2 Months

Shani Agnihotri () Featured

Application Developer and Support Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Python, React Native, Java, C++, MySQL, Mongo DB, JavaScript



Current Designation: Application Developer and Support

Engineer

Current Company: Accenture

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore
Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore,Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Application Developer and Support Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Python, React

Native, Java, C++, MySQL, Mongo DB, JavaScript

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

2.1 years of IT Experience.

Experience in Python ,Scripting ,React Native ,Java ,C++,JavaScript.

Completed CDAC Certification from CDAC acts Bangalore

An excellent communicator with keen analytical ability and information analysis skills proven ability to interact effectively with technical as well as non-technical teams.

Work Experience

Accenture as Application Developer and Support Engineer Jan 2021 to Till Date

Conduent (Oct 2018-Dec 2020)

OCT 2018- TILL DATE: APP dev And Support Engineer, Conduent, Bangalore

Worked on developing Web applications for internal Conduent projects.

Developed scripts in python to automate adding I9 verifiers on Equifax website.

Developed Internal Application using python, Javascript, Html Css using Electron Framework for Internal Auditing.

Projects At Conduent

Equifax Automation: The projects Requires a lot of manual entries into the System for the Recruitment Software Oracle Taleo, This was Automated by creating Bots to handle the Data entry with complete checks in place to avoid any errors. The project was Completed within 4 weeks with successful testing and was deployed within two months in the job.

Technology Used: Python, Selenium Libraries, eel Framework, SQLite.

Approvals App Integration: This was a POC on Integrating Approvals from Our internal Apps that are ICIMS, Oracle HCM CLOUD, Taleo, SAP Fieldglass into One APP .A successful Poc was delivered by me and my team which combined all the Approvals routed to the Managers in a single place where they can be Accessed and Managers can Respond by Accepting, Rejecting Requests adding comments, Approve Inventory, Offers, Absences. The App was delivered in A cross Platform Framework React Native which Helped in getting both los and Android devices to be tested against the App. The App Hits the Available Rest Api's for Approvals and Renders them in a single page Application. The Poc was

delivered over the period of 6 Months.

Several scripts in Python to Handle Production Integrations within very small amount of time and got On spot award for the same

Delivered a successful POC on Conduent Approvals App in order to Manage absences and Compensation modules using React native Application.

Technology Used: React Native, JavaScript, Backend (Python), Rest Api.

ICIMS INTEGRATION: Our Recruitment Process Made a shift from Taleo to ICIMS, so the New Integration Which is still in Progress in Phases, I am responsible for writing scripts for The Termination that occur at different Applications like Oracle HCM Cloud, AIM, SIP and these are Synchronised with ICIMS in order to keep the System Audit Compliant. Various Scripts are in Place to Check daily Process and Bugs, In case there are Problems in the Workflows the Scripts pick them up And Alert the Jira Automatically and these are Picked up and resolved by the Admins, which created a Proactive Behaviour to handle Problems and get them Resolved.

Technology Used: Python, SQLite.

Internal Audit Process Setup For Enterprise Application Services: A new Process was Setup to handle the Internal Auditing on the Roles of the Employees Where these Roles were Being Audited twice within a Quarter, These were setup to Insure that No Terminated, or Unauthorised Employee had access to Internal Applications at Conduent before the Audits Kick off. This was a excruciating Process that Requires the Proof's and Access Verification every Quarter. I was part of the Team to develop the Automated mails to Manager's with the Reports Access Level and get it confirmed. There were two parts Sending Mails and then Reading the response from Outlook. I created the Scripts to Automate the file creation for all the Managers and Mailing Them, Then Collecting Their Response Automatically every Evening, and send this Report to the Audit Team. This was Completed and was put in Production within 2 months.

Technology Used: Python, eel Framework, Outlook Mapl.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya (RGPV), Bhopal in 2017

PG: PG Diploma (Advanced Computing) from Centre for Development of Advanced Computing (CDAC) in 2018

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Python			
React Native			
JAVA			
C++			
MySQL, Mongo DB			
Oracle HCM Cloud			
C, C++			
JavaScript			
HTML5, CSS			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time